Zhu Panpan.
Zhu Zhaifeng.
Zhu Panpan, I'm here.
Zhu Zai, estoy aquí.
Come to find me, Zhu Panpan.
Zhu Chai, ven a buscarme.
I'm coming, Su Chengcheng.
Su Chengcheng, ya vengo.
Class is over!
Ya termina la clase.
Boys and girls,
Chicos.
the first place of the last exam
El primer lugar
goes to
en este examen.
our new classmate
Es la nueva de nuestra clase.
Zhu Panpan again.
Zhu Chai.
Let's give him a big hand.
Démosle un aplauso.
Do you like
¿Les gusta?
your new classmate?
¿Es un nuevo compañero?
Yes!
Sí.
But,
Pero,
since Zhu Panpan
Zhu Chai.
is new in our class,
Porque acabo de trasladarme a la clase.
he is still unfamiliar with everyone,
No estoy muy familiarizado con todos.
so
Por eso,
he seldom speaks.
no habla mucho normalmente.
Can we give him a hand?
¿Podemos ayudarlo?
How about we
y hacer amigos con él?
take the initiative to make friends with him
para que hable más.
and encourage him to speak more?
¿De acuerdo?
Sure!
Bien.
Hello,
Hola.
if you make friends with me,
Si eres mi amigo,
these snacks are all yours.
te daré todos estos bocadillos.
They are yummy.
Son deliciosos.
I'm Wang Lunye.
Me llamo Wang Lun.
If you make friends with me,
Si eres mi amigo,
this is yours,
Esto es para ti.
and I can have the chauffeur
También puedo dejar que nuestro conductor
pick you up to my place.
te recoja.
It's a huge house.
Mi casa es muy grande.
You can come
Cuando llegue el momento,
and play with me.
ven a nuestra casa a jugar.
I'm not going to make friends with you.
No quiero ser tu amigo.
Miss.
Maestro.
Not everyone likes making friends.
No todos quieren hacer amigos.
He can keep silent if he wants.
Si no le gusta hablar, puede no decirlo.
Thank you.
Gracias.
What's your name?
¿Cómo te llamas?
My name is Su Chengcheng.
Me llamo Su Chengcheng.
Zhu…
Zhu...
Zhu Panpan?
Zhu Gai.
Keep dancing.
Salta.
Come on, keep dancing!
¡Salta! ¡Salta!
Zhu Panpan
Zhu Chai
is outstanding in many ways,
Todo está bien.
and he was first again in the last exam.
Ha vuelto a ocupar el primer lugar en este examen.
It's just his personality.
Es su carácter.
He is too shy and timid.
es demasiado introvertido.
It's such…
Así.
It's such a small balloon.
Solo un pequeño globo.
What's the big deal?
No hay nada que temer.
I don't care if the room gets
Hoy no tengo miedo de que la casa esté sucia
dirty or untidy.
ni la casa.
Just stamp on these balloons
Solo pinchas
till all of them are burst.
los globos.
Come on,
Ven.
stamp on them.
Pisa.
Come on!
Ve a pisarlo.
What are you doing?
¿Qué estás esperando?
Mom…
Mamá.
Stop calling me.
No me llames mamá.
Mom just wants you to stamp on them.
Te dejaré pisarlo.
How fun it is!
¡Qué divertido!
Mom…
Mamá.
Come.
Ven.
Just stand there and
Quédate aquí.
watch how to stamp, OK?
Mira cómo pisaré.
Just watch me stamp on them.
Quédate aquí y mírame pisar.
Watch!
Mírame pisar.
Mom.
Mamá.
Come on.
Ven.
Stamp!
Pisa.
- Let me show you. - Mom.
Te enseño.
Come on.
Ven.
Stamp on them in my arms.
Te abrazaré y te pisaré.
Stamp!
Pisa.
Stamp. Son, stamp!
Pisa, hijo. Pisa.
Mom just wants you to stamp on the balloons.
Te dije que pisaras el globo.
Mom.
Mamá.
What's wrong?
¿Qué pasa?
Don't be afraid, my boy.
No tengas miedo, hijo.
Mom…
Mamá.
Zhu Panpan,
Zhu Chai.
why are you still here?
¿Por qué no volviste a casa?
My exam is blown.
Lo arruiné.
I dare not go home.
No me atrevo a volver a casa.
But you got a 99.
Obtuviste 99 puntos.
How is that blown?
y fracasaste.
You are first in our class!
Eres el mejor de la clase.
Look.
Mira.
There is one point deducted,
Se dedujo un punto aquí.
so it's not a 100.
no son 100 puntos.
But I only got 74 .
Mira, solo obtuve 74 puntos.
Don't be afraid.
No tengas miedo.
I'll walk you home.
Te acompaño a casa.
Here you go.
Ya voy.
Refreshing pickled cucumber.
Pequeño pepino.
Enjoy yourselves!
¡Qué rico!
Auntie, it's so yummy.
Señora, está muy rico.
Can I have another bowl of rice?
¿Puedo comer otro tazón?
Yes.
Bien.
Would you like some more?
¿Es suficiente?
No more, thanks.
Sí.
Auntie.
Señora.
If my mom can
Si mi madre pudiera
cook such delicious food,
cocinar tan bien
I can have three full bowls of rice every day.
Puedo comer tres tazones al día.
Enjoy yourself if you like it.
Si te gusta, come más.
Eat this.
Te sirvo la comida.
Mom,
Mamá.
I'd like another bowl, too.
También quiero comer otro tazón.
OK,
Bien.
give me the bowl.
Te lo sirvo.
Auntie, Zhu Panpan is so smart!
Señora, Zhu Li es muy bueno.
Why?
¿Cómo puede ser?
Our last exam is very difficult,
Nuestro examen es muy difícil.
but he's the only one that
Él es el único en la clase.
got a 90 plus.
obtuvo más de 90 puntos.
Really?
¿Sí?
His score is about a dozen points higher
Es más alto
than the second place.
que el segundo.
Our teacher always tells us
Normalmente los maestros nos dejan
to follow his example.
aprender de él.
Auntie, you are such a good mother
Señora, usted es increíble.
that you've educated Zhu Panpan to be so outstanding.
Has cultivado muy bien a Zhu Zai.
And you cook such delicious food.
También cocina muy bien.
Are you a fairy?
¿Eres una hada?
You are the little fairy.
Tú eres la hada.
If you like the food,
¿Te gusta la comida de la tía?
come and enjoy it anytime you want.
Ven a mi casa a menudo.
I've never seen Panpan
Nunca he visto escalar
have the second bowl of rice before.
He comido dos platos
Because of you,
¿Vienes a mi casa?
he has started to enjoy eating.
Él come bien
Here.
Te daré carne.
Have some meat.
Ven.
Want some more, Panpan?
¿Quieres? A escalar.
Eat this.
Te sirvo la comida.
Thanks.
Gracias.
Don't play with Zhu Panpan.
No nos burlemos de Zhu.
Yes, I agree.
Sí, sí.
He's so strange.
Es muy raro.
No wonder he has no friends.
No es de extrañar que no tenga amigos.
One half for you and another half for me.
La mitad para ti y la mitad para mí.
What's the next line?
¿Qué queda?
Oh, right.
Por cierto,
One half for you and another half for me.
La mitad para ti y la mitad para mí.
You are my best friend
Aceptarte eres
forever.
mi mejor amigo.
Let's go to the same senior high school
En el futuro,
and college in the future,
Estudiar en el bachillerato, estudiar en la universidad.
so that we'll be together forever.
para siempre.
Thank you, Su Chengcheng.
Gracias, Su Chengcheng.
Take the most valued thing of mine
Te regalo
as a gift.
para ti.
Then you are my best friend
Acéptalo y también eres
forever, too.
mi mejor amigo.
Cheers.
Salud.
Do you still remember
¿Recuerdas el nombre de
your best friends' names in childhood?
cuando eras niño?
Wang Lunye.
Wang Lun también.
Yuhang.
Yuhang.
Beibei.
Bei.
Mengmeng.
Mengmeng.
And many others.
Hay mucho más.
Is that all?
Se acabó.
You don't know them, anyway.
Te dije que no lo conocías.
That's all.
Nada más.
I like you.
Me gustas.
Repeat.
Repito.
No,
No.
you don't like me at all.
No te gusto.
- I mean… - Don't move.
Soy...
The device is expensive.
El equipo es muy caro.
How do you want me to prove that
¿Cómo quieres que lo pruebe?
I like you?
Me gustas.
Now that you've joined our lab
Ya que viniste a nuestro laboratorio,
and become a member of our research group,
como miembro del equipo de investigación científica,
we should use scientific methods
hay que usar métodos científicos
to prove it.
de manera científica.
Like, do experiments.
Hacer experimentos.
Do experiments
Hacer experimentos
to prove I like you?
para demostrar que me gustas.
Yes.
Sí.
Ms. Chen.
Director Chen.
That's a valuable discussion.
La discusión es muy valiosa.
The research topic of emotion brain-computer interface
Las máquinas emocionales
is also about that.
También es el contenido en este aspecto.
How about
¿Qué tal esto?
you
Simplemente
[Head of Southeast Sci-Tech University Brain and Intelligence Lab]
un experimento.
to see
A ver si
whether it's possible to
si puede
tell whether one is into another
Según los indicios externos,
through external indications?
a través de indicadores externos.
Let's make it the theme
¿Qué te parece
of our next sharing session.
decidimos este tema.
I've always believed that
Siempre pensé que
there are only two results of a declaration of love.
solo hay dos resultados para declararse.
Yes or no.
Aceptar o rechazar.
I didn't see the third one coming:
No esperaba que hubiera un tercer tipo.
do experiments.
Hacer experimentos.
But before the so-called
Pero antes de
love experiment,
antes de que comience el experimento de amor,
I have to…
tengo que...
Chengcheng,
Cheng.
your task for today
Hoy tu misión es
is to clean the lab.
limpiar el laboratorio molecular.
It's so messy.
Esto es demasiado desordenado.
Don't say that,
Hermana Cheng.
Chengcheng.
No es así.
Do you have any idea
No sabes
how many valuable achievements
cuántos resultados experimentales preciosos
are born from the mess?
nacieron en este caos.
You only see the mess
Solo ves el desorden superficial.
without noticing
No.
the serious meaning behind it.
el significado espiritual pesado detrás de él.
Yes, of course.
Es muy pesado.
Oh right, Chengcheng.
Por cierto, Cheng.
It is imperative
Entra al laboratorio molecular.
to put on the lab-gown
Hay que llevar ropa experimental.
before entering the lab.
Ponte guantes de trabajo.
OK.
Bien.
I almost forgot these.
Un pez escapado.
Chengcheng,
Hermana Cheng.
it's cleaned
Todo esto
all by yourself?
tú sola.
Is it up to standard?
¿Estás calificado?
Yes, of course.
Sí.
It's beyond the standard.
Esto es bastante bueno.
Good job.
Esto.
It…
Aquí.
Is also cleaned by me.
Lo limpié todo.
Neat, isn't it?
¿Está limpio?
What?
No.
Well,
Pues...
have you seen
¿Has visto
the oranges on the desk?
las naranjas en la mesa?
Oh, those.
Un pez escapado.
They were thrown away.
Lo tiré.
Thrown away?
¿Lo tiraste?
What?
¿Qué pasa?
They've gone bad.
Está podrido.
They were used to practice suturing
Es la naranja
by our senior,
para practicar.
and now you threw them away.
la tiraste.
If she asks,
Si ella pregunta,
do not mention me.
no me menciones.
I've never been here.
como si nunca hubiera venido.
Jiafa.
Hermano.
Chengcheng.
Hermana Cheng.
Good luck.
Buena suerte.
Is she so terrifying?
¿Dai Meng es tan terrible?
I'm screwed.
Me metí en problemas.
These two
Estos dos
should do.
Más o menos.
There you go.
Lo encontramos.
Miss,
Compañero.
can I use your phone?
Voy a usar mi teléfono.
Robbery!
Robo.
S… Stop!
¡Detente!
Catch...
Agárralo.
Stop him!
¡Deténganlo!
Robbery!
Robo.
You! Stop!
¡Detente!
Stop him!
¡Deténganlo!
Catch him!
¡Atrápenlo!
Robbery!
Robo.
Freeze!
No te muevas.
Thank you.
Gracias, hermana.
You want to use my phone, huh?
¿No me prestaste el celular?
Where's my phone?
¿Dónde está mi celular?
Give it back.
Devuélvemelo.
Where's it?
¿Dónde está el teléfono?
Tell me!
Te estoy preguntando.
Come on,
¿Puedes pensar un poco?
use your head.
Sal.
Clumsy as you, you think
¿Cómo puedes…?
you can get out of this?
¿Crees que eres un ladrón?
How dare you.
¿Robo?
Where's my phone?
¿Dónde está mi celular?
Tell me!
Habla.
Where is it?
¿Dónde lo escondiste?
There are only several pockets.
Solo unos bolsillos.
Here it is.
Es esto.
Thanks.
Gracias, hermana.
Use your head.
Ten cuidado al salir.
Don't move.
No te muevas.
He's yours.
Se lo dejo a ustedes.
OK,
Hola.
we'll have him.
Déjanoslo a nosotros.
Thanks for your help.
Está bien.
Chengcheng.
Cheng.
- Get up. - Did you get your things back?
Levántate.
Yes.
Sí.
They are brought by you?
Lo trajiste tú.
Thank you.
Gracias.
It's not a big deal.
No te ayudé mucho.
Thank you!
Gracias, hermana.
Goodbye!
Adiós, hermana.
She's so cool,
Esta hermana es muy cool.
isn't she?
¿Verdad?
He's Gu Chen, our monitor.
Este es nuestro monitor Gu Chen.
He's very nice,
Tiene muy buen carácter.
always with a mysterious smile.
Siempre tiene una sonrisa encantadora en la cara
Zhu Jiafa,
Jugafa.
where are my oranges?
¿Dónde está mi naranja?
It's her?
Hermana.
Senior Xixi.
Xixi.
What a coincidence!
¡Qué casualidad!
Oranges?
Naranja.
What oranges?
¿Qué naranja?
Those two you use to
Las dos
practice suturing?
que practican coser los hilos de la operación.
I… I don't know.
No, no lo sé.
Senior…
Liuli.
I…
Yo...
I accidentally
Pues...
threw them away
Cuando limpié,
when doing the cleaning.
lo tiré sin querer.
These two are the most similar to the original ones.
Estos dos son los más parecidos que encontré.
Will they do?
¿Qué le parece?
You are new here?
Es nuevo.
You really don't use your head, do you?
Realmente no tienes cerebro.
Who enrolled her?
¿Quién la reclutó?
The standards of our lab
El umbral de nuestro laboratorio
have dropped to this degree?
de nuestro laboratorio?
Now I'm screwed.
Ahora la ofendí.
I wish I will never ever
Espero que
see her again.
no la vuelva a ver.
Oh no,
Se acabó.
please don't tell me she's a member
El experimento de amor de mañana.
of tomorrow's love experiment.
¿Ella también va a participar?
Su Chengcheng.
Su Chengcheng.
Are you ready?
¿Estás listo?
Yes.
Sí.
Obvious change in heart rate.
La frecuencia cardíaca ha cambiado considerablemente.
0.5℃ higher in body temperature.
La temperatura corporal aumenta 0,5 grados centígrados.
Higher body temperature,
La temperatura corporal aumenta.
dilated pupils,
Ampliación de las pupilas
increased heart rate,
Acelera la frecuencia cardíaca.
and faster blood flow.
La sangre sube.
Aren't all of these
¿No es todo
the demonstrations of a crush?
que te gusta alguien?
You still don't believe I like you?
¿No puede probar que me gustas?
There's something wrong with the experiment design.
Hay un problema con el diseño experimental.
The changes in your physiological data
Ahora tus datos fisiológicos
don't have to be the signs
no puede revelar directamente
of a crush.
con las emociones que te gusto.
They can also be resulted from
Es posible.
external stimuli.
debido a la estimulación externa.
We need a control group.
Hay que agregar un equipo de comparación.
Control group?
Equipo de comparación.
Who?
¿Con quién?
Have you finished?
¿Terminaste?
Higher body temperature,
Aumenta la temperatura corporal.
dilated pupils,
Ampliación de las pupilas
increased heart rate,
Aumenta la frecuencia cardíaca
and faster blood flow.
La sangre aumenta.
How?
¿Qué pasa?
Wait.
Espera.
You can't
Creo que tu conclusión
jump to the conclusion
es demasiado apresurada.
just based on
No puedes
the changes in my data
mis datos han cambiado.
just now.
significa que no me gustas.
Under the same condition,
En el mismo ambiente,
the changes in the data.
cuando te enfrentas a Xixi,
of your body temperature,
tu temperatura corporal
pupil size,
El tamaño de las pupilas, la frecuencia cardíaca y la sangre.
heart rate and blood flow
Los datos del cuerpo
are much greater
son mucho más altos
when you were facing Senior Xixi.
cuando experimenté.
What?
¿Qué?
You like Zhang Xixi?
¿Te gusta Zhang Xixi?
Xiao Yuhe.
Hermano.
Is the experiment
¿Quieres que haga experimentos contigo?
only your excuse
para demostrar que me gustas.
to
¿Es solo una excusa
reject me?
para rechazarme?
You didn't even prove you are fond of me.
No has demostrado que te gusto.
How can I respond?
¿Cómo te respondo?
I will prove it to you.
Te lo demostraré.
I want ten ox tendons,
Quiero diez tendones de pata de res.
ten bull backstraps,
Diez tendones de ternera.
ten lamb kebabs,
Diez brochetas de cordero.
five squids,
Cinco calamares.
five gristles,
Cinco huesos crujientes.
two bean curd rolls…
Dos rollos de tofu.
Wait a minute,
Espera un momento.
how are you going to finish them all?
¿Puedes comerlo todo?
Even a pig can't.
Los cerdos tampoco pueden terminar.
Don't worry.
Te tengo a ti.
I've got you.
¿No comes?
And two chicken wings.
Dos alitas de pollo más.
50, 51, 52.
50, 51, 52.
Come on.
Hermana.
You have eaten
Has comido
too much.
toda mi vida.
Stop eating.
No comas.
No,
No.
I feel sad.
No estoy feliz.
I need to produce dopamine by eating
Necesito comer para repartir dopamina.
so that I can feel better.
Si no, no estaría feliz.
But I think Xiao Yuhe
No, creo que
was right.
Tienes razón.
Think about it.
Piénsalo.
You only knew him several days ago
Solo los conoces unos días.
and you told him you like him.
Dile que te gusta.
I wouldn't believe it if I were him.
No lo creo.
How can I not know
Entonces, ¿quién me gusta?
who I like?
quién me gusta?
- You don't know. - I do know.
No lo sabes.
Listen, Li Meizi,
Li Meizi, escucha.
I'm going back to the dorm.
Voy a volver al dormitorio ahora.
I'll stay up studying,
Voy a desafiar las luces y la noche.
and find out the evidence
Quiero leer todos los libros.
to prove Xiao Yuhe's refutation
Voy a decirle a Xiao Yuhe
is also wrong.
También está mal que me refute.
I'm going.
Ahora voy.
The barbecue!
Pinchos.
Hello,
Hola.
I'm Musk.
Soy Marsk.
Yes!
Genial.
Start scanning.
Empieza a escanear.
Xiao Yuhe,
River Xiao.
[Musk  Developed by: Xiao Yuhe]
Estás feliz ahora.
You are excited.
Emocionada.
Who didn't lock the door?
¿Quién se va o no cierra la puerta?
Some say
Dicen que
love is a well-matched game,
el amor es una competición entre iguales.
but in this uneven-matched game
En esta batalla
of mine,
en esta batalla
I will die
Incluso si muero,
for love.
moriré por el ataque.
Good morning, Jiafa.
Buenos días, hermano.
Chengcheng,
Hermana Cheng.
didn't I tell you
¿No te lo dije ayer?
not to have food or drinks in the office?
que no se puede comer en la oficina.
I'm sorry, Jiafa.
Lo siento, hermano.
I'll have it outside.
Voy a comer afuera.
Wait.
Espera.
Why are you using a spoon
Toma un té con leche.
instead of a straw
¿Por qué no necesitas pajitas?
to drink bubble tea?
Usa una cuchara.
There are plenty of toppings in it.
Tengo mucho té con leche.
Like crushed peanuts,
Mira, hay maní dentro.
raisins,
Y las uvas secas.
coconut jelly, pudding,
Hay coco y tela.
and some other toppings.
Hay algo más abajo.
I can't suck them in with a straw.
No puedo respirar con una pajita.
And it's called bubble tea?
¿Cómo se llama té con leche?
Why not grass jelly?
¿Por qué no te llamas hierba de hadas?
They are different.
¿Es lo mismo que quemar la hierba de hadas?
I bought one and got one free.
Una por una en la tienda de té con leche.
Would you like to try?
¿Quieres probarlo?
No, no,
No.
thanks.
No hace falta.
See?
Mira.
I can suck them in.
Puedo absorberlo.
You're good.
Eres increíble.
If you like it,
Si te gusta,
I can always bring you one cup
te compraré té con leche
when I buy it.
te traeré un vaso.
She's nice.
Muy bien.
These days,
Estos días,
you don't understand.
hay cosas que no entiendes.
I didn't mean to…
No quise...
Prof. Du.
Profesor Du.
Xiao Yuhe,
Hermano.
I did a lot of research
Anoche
last night.
Revisé mucha información.
To tell
para juzgar a una persona
whether one is into another
para juzgar
through physiological data
si te gusta otra persona.
is a one-way experiment.
es unilateral.
When you are into someone,
Cuando te gusta alguien,
your heart beats faster,
mi corazón late más rápido.
you have a higher blood oxygen level,
La concentración de oxígeno en sangre aumenta.
and produce more hormones.
La secreción hormona aumenta.
But we can't jump to the conclusion
Pero una persona
that one is into another
después de estas situaciones,
based on
no puede revelar
these simple changes.
Está atrapado en el amor.
So
Por eso,
even if
cuando estaba haciendo experimentos contigo,
all my experimental data
aunque todos mis datos
meet the requirements,
todos mis datos,
I still can't prove I'm into you.
No puede probar que me gustas.
You are making me prove
Me estás haciendo probar
something that cannot be proved.
que no puede ser probado.
Seems you really did a lot of research.
Parece que has hecho muchas tareas.
It is impossible to prove
Si te gusta alguien,
whether one is into another.
no se puede probar.
What do you mean?
¿Qué quieres decir?
You are in favor of me?
Me estás apoyando.
We can't prove whether one is into another,
El amor no puede ser probado
but we can observe it.
pero se puede observar.
In 2003,
El laboratorio de Helen Fescher
Helen Fisher and her lab members
En 2003,
scanned the brains of 17 couples
escaneó el cerebro de 17 parejas
through MRI
el cerebro de las 17 parejas.
and found apparent activation
Los encontré.
in the ventral tegmentum and caudate nucleus
Al observar las fotos de la pareja,
of the midbrain
el abdomen de la zona cerebral
when they looked at
La zona cubierta y la zona final
the photos of their partners.
y la zona final.
And the more they love each other,
Y cuanto más amas,
the more active
las actividades de estas dos regiones
the two areas are.
será más fuerte.
So through observation on
Así que a través de la observación,
the two areas
si estas dos regiones están activadas.
we can tell whether
para juzgar
one is into the other.
si le gusta otra persona.
We need to redo the experiment.
Tenemos que hacer el experimento de nuevo.
Again?
y hacer experimentos.
When we were
Cuando hicimos
doing the NIR brain function imaging,
la prueba de imágenes cerebrales,
the ventral tegmentum
la zona cubierta de tu abdomen
and caudate nucleus of your midbrain were not activated.
y la zona final.
You explained
Dijiste que
it was due to the ambience in the lab,
el ambiente del laboratorio no es bueno.
so we can cultivate the ambience
La próxima vez,
between us before
antes de recopilar datos,
the next data collection.
antes de recopilar datos.
What do you mean?
¿Qué quieres decir?
I mean going on a date,
Es una cita.
doing something
hacer cosas
common for couples
entre parejas.
to get us closer
para aumentar la intimidad entre nosotros.
so that
Así que estás haciendo
the relative functional areas
resonancia magnética funcional.
in your brain
Durante la prueba de imágenes,
will be fully activated
la zona funcional correspondiente del cerebro
when doing the NIR imaging.
se activará más.
A date…
¿Una cita?
You can decide
Puedes pensar
the places you want to go
si hay algún lugar al que quieras ir.
and the things you want to do.
Si quieres hacer algo,
Just let me know when you have decided.
Dime cuando estés lista.
OK.
Bien.
My friends,
Hermanas.
he asked me out.
Me invitó a una cita.
On his own initiative.
Me lo dijo él.
Have you decided where to go?
¿Has decidido a dónde vas?
I did some research.
Lo investigué.
Red Brick Art Museum will do.
El museo de arte de ladrillos rojos es bastante bueno.
There will be
Además, recientemente hay
an installation art exhibition recently.
una exposición de arte de dispositivos.
It'll be nice
Creo que después de ver la exposición,
to sit
después de ver la exposición.
in the coffee shop nearby
Siéntate.
after seeing the exhibition.
Creo que es bastante interesante.
You are good.
Bien.
You really did a lot of research.
¿Hiciste una guía?
That hurts.
Pensé que me golpeaste.
Chengcheng.
Cheng.
Meizi.
Meizi.
Monitor.
Monitor.
The assignment of physics should be handed in tomorrow.
Es hora de entregar los deberes mañana.
And the time for the English test is also fixed.
También ha bajado la hora de la prueba de inglés.
Only you two didn't reply in the class group.
Veo que solo ustedes dos no respondieron al grupo.
Oh God, stop, don't mention it.
Dios mío. Basta, basta.
Didn't we just finish the internship
Estudiaremos en el tercer trimestre.
of Electronic Technology
en el semestre trimestral.
of the second semester of the freshman year?
¿No acaba de terminar?
And we handed in the assignments
Acabamos de entregar las estadísticas hace unos días.
of Mathematic Statistics and biology a few days ago.
y biología.
I feel like I'm in Grade 12.
¿Estoy en el tercer grado?
I can't believe that.
Estudiantes de bachillerato.
We are
Nosotros...
paying the tuition for one person,
pagar la matrícula de una persona.
having a curriculum for two people,
Aprender clases de dos personas.
and doing assignments for four people.
Escribe los deberes de cuatro personas.
One minute there are assignments and exams,
Este es el examen de deberes.
and the next there are experiments in the lab.
Allá es el laboratorio.
I'm exhausted.
Es muy difícil para mí.
But speaking of the lab,
Pero, Cheng,
Chengcheng,
Hablando del laboratorio,
the Brain and Intelligence Lab you picked
El cerebro y la inteligencia que elegiste
is a national key subject.
es la prioridad nacional.
It's a good opportunity.
una buena oportunidad.
Come on.
No lo menciones.
All the members in my team are talented
Nuestro laboratorio está lleno de crack.
except me.
Soy el único plato.
Tell you what,
Además,
there's a horrible senior
en nuestro laboratorio
in our lab...
Hay una hermana que da mucho miedo.
How come such a pretty face like you
Te veo muy limpia.
is so brazen?
¿Por qué eres tan malo?
You will be over any boy you like,
Cuando ves a un chico que te gusta,
won't you?
pégalo hacia adelante.
Who do you think you are to pursue Wang Jiaze?
¿También puedes perseguir a Wang Jiaze?
How dare she?
¿Cómo te atreves?
Stop being mad.
No te vuelvas loco.
Calm yourself down.
Cálmate.
Will she think it was me
No pensará que
who gave the cup to her?
que se lo di yo?
What should I do?
¿Qué hago?
Chengcheng.
Cheng.
Give it to her.
Toma, ve.
- I don't dare. - Talk to her.
No me atrevo.
Just go!
Ve rápido.
Senior.
Hermana.
Um…
Pues...
- There's some tissue. - Don't follow me.
Hay papel.
Jiafa.
Hermano Gafa
OK, I'm on my way.
Bien, ahora vengo.
I just heard that
Acabo de escuchar que
you joined our lab
viniste al laboratorio.
all for
Tu propósito
dating Xiao Yuhe.
para estar con Xiao Yu en la orilla del río.
I don't understand.
Estoy un poco confundido.
Do you think this lab
¿Crees que este laboratorio
is suitable for you to date someone
es adecuado para tu pareja?
or
O
you feel like dating someone
al entrar en este laboratorio,
once you enter the lab?
cuando entras en este laboratorio.
Why don't you speak?
¿Qué significa que no hablas?
You think I'm giving you a hard time?
¿Crees que te estoy poniendo difícil?
Do not distract him.
No te equivoques.
Do you know
¿Sabes?
how much hope we have placed
cuántas esperanzas
on Xiao Yuhe?
al Río Xiaoyu?
Do you know
¿Sabes?
how precious
qué precioso
his time for experiment is?
es muy valioso.
Stop doing that.
No hagas tonterías.
Is there anything else?
¿Tienes algo que hacer?
You can go then.
No pasa nada. Vamos.
Goodbye, sir.
Adiós, profesor.
Su Chengcheng,
Su Chengcheng.
have you decided on the location for the experiment?
¿Has pensado en el lugar del experimento?
I have so many things to do
Tengo muchas cosas que hacer hoy.
that I haven't decided.
No he tenido tiempo de pensarlo.
Then leave it to me.
Entonces no lo pienses.
I'll let you know when I have decided.
Pensé que te lo diría.
No wonder he's
El cerebro del crack
a curve wrecker.
Es diferente.
Cultivating ambience
para crear un ambiente de citas.
to get closer,
y aumentar la intimidad.
monitoring the physiological data and brain movements.
Detección de señales físicas y cerebrales.
Just admit you are into her.
Me gusta si te gusta.
Why does it have to be so roundabout?
¿Por qué eres tan indiferente?
Right?
¿Verdad?
Into me?
¿Te gusto?
Are you sure?
No puede ser.
It's natural for a man
Los hombres
to be indirect
A veces es así.
in his confession
Lo siento.
of love.
Expresa sus sentimientos directamente.
Chengcheng.
Cheng.
Have you decided
¿A dónde vas a jugar?
where you are going on a date?
¿Está decidido?
No, I haven't.
Todavía no.
Bro Ying,
Ying
where are you going?
¿A dónde vas?
The course Prof. Du teaches is a little difficult.
La clase del profesor Du es un poco difícil.
I've borrowed
Lo pedí prestado.
the notes of a senior
las notas de la estudiante del último año.
and plan to preview the lessons.
Planeo repasar con anticipación.
I'll go with you.
Entonces voy contigo.
I plan to preview, too.
También quiero estudiar.
Can I borrow the notes?
Préstame las notas más tarde.
Sure.
Vale.
How diligent.
Los buenos estudiantes son buenos estudiantes.
It's so late and they still work hard.
¿Por qué sales a estudiar tan tarde?
Where were we?
¿De qué estábamos hablando?
Your date.
Hablando de tu cita.
Ask him!
Ve a preguntar.
You need to know where is the date
Tienes que saber a dónde vas.
and what to wear.
y qué te vas a poner.
I'll look impatient if so.
Parece que soy demasiado activa.
The place of the date is the amusement park.
Lugar de cita, parque de atracciones.
I'll see you out of your dorm
Mañana a las dos de la tarde.
at 2:00 PM tomorrow.
Nos vemos abajo del dormitorio.
Su Chengcheng!
Su Cheng.
Zhu Panpan!
Zhu Zhaifeng.
I'm here.
Estoy aquí.
Come.
Ven.
Zhu Panpan,
Zhu Zai.
I'm here!
Estoy aquí.
Su Chengcheng!
Su Chengcheng.